// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Arjun Reddy",
    options: [
      "Arjun Reddy",
      "Andhari vadu",
      "A1 Express",
      "Aacharya"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Race Gurram",
    options: [
      "Gem",
      "Race 2",
      "Galodu",
      "Race Gurram"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Avengers End Game",
    options: [
      "Terminator",
      "The Avengers",
      "Avengers Infinity War",
      "Avengers End Game"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Hello",
    options: [
      "Idharammayilatho",
      "Calling sahasra",
      "Tik Tik Tik",
      "Hello"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Jai Lava Kusha",
    options: [
      "option 1",
      "option 2",
      "Jai Lava Kusha",
      "option 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Oopiri",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Oopiri",
      "option 3",
      "option 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Fidha",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "option 2",
      "Fidha",
      "option 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Agfe Of Ultron",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "option 2",
      "option 3",
      "Agfe Of Ultron"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Paisa Vasool",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Paisa Vasool",
      "option 3",
      "option 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " ",
    answer: "Chandhamama Kathalu",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "option 2",
      "option 3",
      "Chandhamama Kathalu"
    ]
  },
];